Marcello Annicchiarico

Software Engineer

I'm a 37-year-old Software Engineer with over 10 years of experience in development, user interface, graphic design, data visualization, and progressive web app. I invite you to discover more about me by visiting my website: marcellokabora.com

EXPERIENCE

<u>LINUS Finance</u>, Berlin — Software Engineer

Sep 2021 - Aug 2022

LINUS Finance is one of the leaders in Real Estate in Germany. I started work with the core of the team rebuilding the new UI, working on the new registration, creating the template of the product, and building different landing pages for the marketing team.

Buildingminds, Berlin — Frontend Developer

Jan 2020 - Aug 2021

BuildingMinds believes in empowering the real estate industry with advanced digital solutions, building an application with Angular and Microsoft services. I worked on the implementation of many features moving around different teams, focusing on different components and the creation of the appmanament.

<u>Yukkalab</u>, Berlin — Frontend Developer

Jun 2017 - Nov 2019

Yukkalab is an application for desktop and mobile that uses different frameworks such as Angular, Firebase, Highchart, and D3 to build interesting visualizations like the Network, Chartmap, or Signals. By analyzing and evaluating high-quality news you will gain an insight into the stock markets.

<u>Smava</u>, Berlin — Frontend Developer

Feb 2016 - Nov 2016

Smava provides the best solution in Germany to find the right credit online with more than 50 bank accounts. My position as Frontend Developer was fundamental for the creation of the new homepage. I worked on all the animation in jquery and for the mail campaign. I also have a letter of recommendation from my manager Martin Cichowski after I left the company.

Tanglang, Viareggio — Fullstack Developer

Apr 2014 - Dec 2015

Tang Lang Viaggi provides the best travel on a bus to all European events, like Oktoberfest, Cosmoprof, IAA, Geneva, Christmas, Lloret De Mar, and others in all of Europe. My job as a Full Stack Developer was to build 6 websites for different events

INFO

Born: 13.04.1985 in Italy Milano Address: Germany Berlin 10785 Website: marcellokabora.com Email: marcellokabora@gmail.com Account: Linkedin, Github, Stackoverflow, Twitter, Youtube

SKILL

Nodejs, Angular, React, jQuery, PHP, Sass, Material, Semantic, Bootstrap, D3, Highcharts, Formly, Firebase, AWS, MySQL, Git, NPM, VSC, Photoshop, Illustrator, Ckeditor, PWA, WordPress, Chrome, Safari, Edge, Slack, Github, Gitlab, Jira, Azure, Miro, Figma, Storybook, CMS.

LANGUAGE

English, Italian, Spanish

HOBBIE

Graphic Design, Minimal Art, Music Production, Technology, Architect, Interior Design, Beach Volley, Soccer, Ping Pong. in Europe with the same designs and provide a different theme for each event with a complex form for purchasing the event.

Maggiolino, Viareggio — Fullstack Developer

Aug 2013 - Jan 2015

Maggiolino is an eCommerce <u>website</u> where anyone can find and buy specific books online. My position as Full Stack Developer required me to build the new website from scratch using jQuery and MySql following the google image visualization.

Annunci Animali, Viareggio — Frontend Developer

Mar 2013 - Oct 2014

Annunci Animali is the biggest and most famous website in Italy for selling or buying your animal, most of all dogs and cats but also other animals. My position inside the company was as Frontend Designer where I designed the homepage and most of the landing page of the website.

Airesis, Viareggio — UI Designer

Apr 2011 - Apr 2012

Airesis is an open-source democracy <u>platform</u> where anyone can open a discussion and involve users to vote and discuss it. My position inside the company was UI/UX Designer and I worked with them for 6 months.

Shipchandler, Viareggio — UI Designer

Jan 2009 - Feb 2010

Shipchandler is a metallurgic company focused on boat furniture, my position as UI designer was necessary for the branding of the company, I created all the business cards of the employers and a few catalogs for the products of the company.

EDUCATION

Guglielmo Marconi, *Middle School*

SEP 2007 - JUN 2012

PROJECT

Beathecue — Friend

June 2021 - Present

Marcellokabora — Portfolio

Jan 2022 - Present

Yawiki — Timeline

Feb 2013 - Sep 2014

Wokamoka — Avatar

Jan 2010 - Sep 2011